Guide to the Michael Kahn Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 1992 Acquisition, 1947-1985; 1; 30.71; (33 boxes)
  - Production and Administrative Files, 1959-1979
    - Scripts, 1971-1988
      - "The Woman from Tacna," playscript by Mario Vargas Llosa, undated (Box 17)
    - Publicity and production materials
      - "Notes on The training of the Actor" by Michel Saint Denis, photocopy, 1968 (Box 17)
      - Juilliard School, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
      - Theatre training and teaching papers, 1984 (Box 17)
      - "The Marketing Area for McCarter Theatre," report, 1974 July 18 (Box 17)
      - Papers pertaining to Thornton Wilder plays, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
      - American Shakespeare Theatre brochures/schedules 1970-1972 Season, 3 (Box 17)
      - Actors correspondence, 1968-1970; 2 (Box 18)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1969 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
      - "Advance," correspondence, 1971 (Box 18)
      - Casting, 1971-1972; 2 (Box 18)
      - Talent Agent letters of referral, 1968-1970 (Box 18)
      - Fan mail, 1968-1971; 6 (Box 18)
      - Memorabilia, 1974, undated (Box 18)
        Includes zinnia seed packet, Maine Antique Dealer brochure, map of Quebec and Metropolitan Opera ticket stubs, keys and a marble.
      - Health insurance papers, circa 1976 (Box 18)
      - Check register, undated (Box 18)
      - Russell, Henry, undated (Box 18)
        Includes letter, photograph and envelope
      - Wittington, Gene, photographs and CV, undated (Box 18)
      - "The Death of Punchinello," correspondence, photograph and transparency, 1977 (Box 18)
      - Carnaby Street, photograph, undated (Box 18)
      - Film production photographs, undated (Box 18)
        Includes 2 photographs from Streetcar Named Desire, and 1 photograph from The Lady From Shanghai.
      - Unsorted production materials, 7 (Box 18)
      - Unsorted production materials, 1968-1985; 15 (Box 19)
      - American Shakespeare Theatre, brochures and schedules, 1971-1972; 2 (Box 19)
      - Shakespeare festivals, 1969-1971 (Box 19)
      - Programs, brochures, printed material, 1968-1979; 5 (Box 20)
      - Clippings, 1972-1979; 3 (Box 20)
      - Publicity, 1975; 2 (Box 20)
      - News releases, other theatres, 1970-1971; 5 (Box 20)
    - [Expanding file 3], 1967
      - The Owl Answers, 1965 (Box 21)
      - The Rattle of a Simple Man, 1966 (Box 21)
      - What Color Goes with Brown, 1966 (Box 21)
      - The Portable Phoenix Tour, 1966 (Box 21)
      - You Can't Take it With You, 1966 (Box 21)
      - Measure for Measure, 1966, 1973; 3 (Box 21)
      - The Wilder plays, 1977 (Box 21)
      - Portable Phoenix 2, 1966 (Box 21)
      - Rimers of Eldritch, 1967 (Box 21)
      - Portable Phoenix 3, 1967 (Box 21)
      - The Merchant of Venice, 1967; 3 (Box 21)
      - The Cavern, 1967 (Box 21)
      - "Vernon Rice, Henry Hewes, Nom Bests, etc.", 1967 (Box 21)
      - Antony and Cleopatra, 1967 (Box 21)
      - Wait Until Dark, 1967 (Box 21)
      - Harpers Bazaar, 1967 (Box 21)
      - The Freaking Out of Stephanie Blake, 1967 (Box 21)
      - East of Eden - 'Pre', 1966 (Box 21)
      - Here's Where I Belong, 1967 (Box 21)
    - Subject files
      - American Shakespeare Festival reviews, 1967 (Box 21)
      - Casting, 1966-1975; 5 (Box 21)
      - City Center Acting Company, 1973-1974 (Box 21)
      - Programs, brochures and magazines, 1973-1975; 4 (Box 22)
      - General correspondence, 1965-1973; 3 (Box 22)
      - Designer resumes, 1979 (Box 22)
      - Eisen, Max, 1973 (Box 22)
      - The First Folio of the Performing Arts magazine, 1973 (Box 22)
      - Goodman Theatre, 1971-1972; 2 (Box 22)
      - Health records, 1978-1979 (Box 22)
      - Joseph Verner Reed, 1968-1973 (Box 22)
      - Juilliard, 1968-1971; 4 (Box 22)
        Includes catalogues, schedules and correspondence
      - Juilliard, 1971-1973; 3 (Box 23)
      - Kahn photographs, undated (Box 23)
      - The Kennedy Center, 1973; 3 (Box 23)
      - McCarter Theatre, clippings, 1979 (Box 23)
      - Memos, 1969-1973; 2 (Box 23)
      - News - Stratford theater clippings, 1973 (Box 23)
      - News releases - other theatres, 1972-1973; 2 (Box 23)
      - Office of Advanced Drama Research, re: Ballet, 1971-1972 (Box 23)
      - Plans and planning, 1973-1974; 2 (Box 23)
      - Press, 1973-1974; 3 (Box 23)
        Includes clippings, correspondence and printed material
      - Unsorted production materials, 1970 (Box 23)
      - General publicity, 1973; 4 (Box 24)
      - University of Michigan, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
      - Set design drawings reproductions, 1970-1976 (Box 24)
        Productions include: After the Fall, Don Carlo, The Hostage, Canterbury Tales, Guys and Dolls, Macbeth, and Rosmersholm
    - Publicity and production materials
      - All's Well That Ends Well, 1970-1973; 5 (Box 24)
      - As You Like It, 1976; 3 (Box 24)
      - Beyond the Horizon, 1975; 2 (Box 24)
      - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, 1974-1975; 5 (Box 24)
      - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, 2 (Box 25)
      - The Country Wife, 1973; 2 (Box 25)
      - The Crucible, 1976; 2 (Box 25)
      - The Devil's Disciple, 1970 (Box 25)
      - The Epic of Buster Friend, 1973-1974; 2 (Box 25)
      - Hamlet, 1969-1970 (Box 25)
      - Henry IV, undated (Box 25)
        Playscript by Luigi Pirandello, a new translation by David Calicchio
      - Julius Caesar, 1973 (Box 25)
      - Long Day's Journey Into Night, 1977 (Box 25)
      - Macbeth, 1973; 2 (Box 25)
      - Romeo and Juliet, 1974 (Box 25)
      - 'Tis Pity She's a Whore, 1975 (Box 25)
      - Twelfth Night, 1974 (Box 25)
      - A Winter's Tale, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1985
    Includes personal and business correspondence.
    - Balls, Miss Crystal, 1971-1972; 2 (Box 26)
    - Havoc, June, 1975 (Box 26)
    - Lansbury, Angela, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
    - Pleasence, Donald, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
    - Sand, Günther, 1964-1965; 11 (Box 26)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1973 (Box 26)
    - "Actors' correspondence", 1974-1979; 15 (Box 26)
    - "Famous personalities", 1972-1975 (Box 26)
    - Fan mail, 1974-1976; 3 (Box 27)
    - General correspondence, 1953-1963; 21 (Box 27)
    - General correspondence, 1965-1971; 27 (Box 28)
    - General correspondence, 1972-1978; 23 (Box 29)
    - General correspondence, 1979-1985, undated; 14 (Box 30)
  - Personal Papers and Effects, 1947-1975
    - Birth certificate, photocopy, circa 1971 (Box 30)
    - Passport, 1961-[?] (Box 30)
    - Tax documents, 1968-1973; 2 (Box 30)
    - Insurance policy, 1976 (Box 30)
    - Financial records, 1972, 1975; 4 (Box 30)
      Includes bills, invoices and receipts
    - Diary, circa 1947 (Box 30)
    - Journal, 1955-1956 (Box 30)
    - Notebooks, 1968-1969 (Box 30)
    - Juilliard course notes, 1968-1969 (Box 30)
    - Improvisation class notes, 1st year, 1969-1970 (Box 30)
    - Appointment book, 1965 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1967-1975 (Box 30)
    - Memorabilia, undated (Box 30)
      Includes pin, hotel notepads, and train schedule
    - Postage stamps, undated (Box 30)
    - Luggage tags, undated (Box 30)
    - Picture hangers, undated (Box 30)
    - Clipboards, undated; 2 (Box 30)
    - Shaving mirror, undated (Box 31)
    - Small curio box containing paper clips, undated (Box 31)
    - Photographs and negatives of Michael Kahn, undated; 7 (Box 31)
  - Sound Recordings, 1971-1973
    Conditions Governing Access
    Reel-to-reel audio recordsings: Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    Three 7" reel-to-reel audio recordings.
    - J. M. Marshall interview with Michael Kahn, insert for American Shakespeare Festival Spotlight no. 134 for Voice of America, 1971 August 26; 1; 00:07:49; Static and a high amount of hiss can be heard on this audiotape reel. (Box 32 (Restricted Fragile), Item barcode 39002091394834)
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "Airshow--Spotlight" with Michael Kahn, American Shakespeare Festival, for Voice of America, 1972 August 8; 1; 00:10:03 (Box 32 (Restricted Fragile), Item barcode 39002091394842)
    - "Opening Events--Kennedy Center, Third Season," interview with Michael Kahn, American Shakespeare Theatre, for Voice of America, 1973 September 6; 1; 00:09:41 (Box 32 (Restricted Fragile), Item barcode 39002091394859)
      There is a note written by Jeanne Marshall to Michael Kahn dated 1973-09-10. It reads: Dear Michael Kahn, As always you were brilliant. It made for a marvelous interview...receiving comments here, the mildest of which was: "splendid". A million thanks. There's a copy for your files via [Leo]. Much Love, Jeanne.
  - Oversize, 1968, undated
    - Four set design sketches, unidentified, undated (Box 33 (Oversize))
    - Unidentified production photograph, undated (Box 33 (Oversize))
    - American Shakespeare Festival Theatre programs, 1968 (Box 33 (Oversize))
- June 1994 Acquisition, 1927-1986; 2; 5.67; (9 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  Production materials, correspondence, personal and subject files, and photographs relating to Michael Kahn's theatrical activities.
  - Production Materials, 1945-1986
    - Carmen, 1980, undated; 7 (Box 34)
    - Carousel, 1945, 1984; 4 (Box 34)
    - Photograph of Tennesse Williams and Michael Kahn during production of Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, circa 1970 (Box 34)
    - A Doll's House, 1979 (Box 34)
    - "Eve of the Trial," playscript by Tennesse Williams, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Happy End, 1972 (Box 34)
    - "Film Festival," book for a musical by Adrienne Kennedy, typescript, 1984 (Box 34)
    - Madame Butterfly, 1983 (Box 34)
    - Our Town, undated (Box 34)
    - Senorita from Tacna, 1983 (Box 34)
    - Showboat, circa 1983; 3 (Box 34)
    - Showboat, 1925-1983; 7 (Box 35)
      Also includes set design photographs, and sheet music for "'Ol Man River."
    - Songs ("Sleepsong" and "Viola") by Craig Lucas and Gerald Busby, undated; 2 (Box 35)
    - Whodunnit, 1982; 2 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence and Subject Files, 1979-1986
    - Professional correspondence, 1979-1984; 6 (Box 35)
    - The Acting Company, 1983-1985; 3 (Box 35)
    - Student actors writing exercises, 1979-1986; 2 (Box 35)
    - The American College Theatre Festival, printed material, 1982-1983 (Box 35)
    - Chautauqua, 1984; 2 (Box 36)
    - Colorado Shakespeare Festival, 1981 (Box 36)
    - Houston Grand Opera, 1980 (Box 36)
    - Kahn in Boulder, Colorado, 1981; 2 (Box 36)
    - Set design drawings and photographs, undated; 2 (Box 36)
    - Stage photographs of Michael Kahn and actors, undated (Box 36)
    - Unsorted production materials, 1979-1985, undated; 10 (Box 36)
    - Notes and notepads, undated; 2 (Box 36)
  - Personal Papers, 1974-1986; 2
    - Correspondence, 1979-1981; 2 (Box 36)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1986; 11 (Box 37)
    - Legal and financial records, 1974-1983; 3 (Box 37)
    - The Dakota [residence], 1980 (Box 37)
    - Contracts (Box 37)
    - Family photograph, undated (Box 37)
    - Unidentified photograph, undated (Box 37)
  - Printed Material, 1927-1984
    - Theater production programs, 1927-1931, 1984; 2 (Box 37)
    - Magazines, 1979-1983 (Box 37)
    - American Quilts and Coverlets, undated (Box 38)
    - Souvenir program for Gloria Steinem's 50th birthday, 1984 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous printed material, 1982-1984; 3 (Box 38)
      Includes theatre and festival brochures and stage production programs.
    - Press clippings, 1968-1981; 9 (Box 38)
    - Playbill cards, 1982-1983 (Box 38)
      "PLAYBILL is pleased to present the sixth series of 'PLAYBILL CARDS' portraying the cover and opening night cast pages of PLAYBILL in the 1982-1983 Broadway Season." (2 sets)
  - Personal Items, undated
    - Eye cover mask and book of matches, undated (Box 38)
    - Containers, plastic bags, undated (Box 38)
  - Oversize, 1955-1988
    - "The Cowboy and the Fiddler," score by Sam Raphling, photocopy, undated (Box 39 (Oversize))
    - Photograph of unidentified man, undated (Box 39 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook, 1955-1967 (Box 40 (Oversize))
    - Two briefcases, undated (Box 41 (Oversize))
    - Clippings, 1983-1988; 6 (Box 42 (Oversize))
    - Set designs
      - Henry V, 1968 (Box 43 (Broadside))
      - A New Way to Pay Old Debts, undated (Box 43 (Broadside))
- July 1998 Acquisition, 1943-1999; 3; 27.95; (32 boxes)
  Correspondence, production and subject files, audiovisual and printed material primarily relating to Kahn's work at the Shakespeare Theatre in Washington D.C.
  - Production files, 1943, 1986-1998
    Includes scripts, contracts, performance reports, reviews, cast lists, set and costume designs, historical background and related papers
    - All's Well That Ends Well, 1987, 1996; 8 (Box 44)
    - Antony and Cleopatra, 1988-1996; 5 (Box 44)
    - As You Like It, 1989-1997; 10 (Box 44)
    - The Beggar's Opera, undated (Box 44)
    - Carmen, 1982 (Box 44)
    - The Comedy of Errors, 1992-1993; 12 (Box 44)
    - Coriolanus, 1991; 13 (Box 44)
    - The Devil's Disciple, 1996 (Box 45)
    - The Doctor's Dilemma, 1994; 17 (Box 45)
    - The Duchess of Malfi, 1989; 4 (Box 45)
    - "Ambivalence: the Dialectic of the Histories", undated (Box 45)
    - Elektra, 1943, 1989; 3 (Box 45)
    - Five by Tenn, 1986; 2 (Box 45)
    - Fuente Ovejuna, 1991 (Box 45)
    - "The Ghost Dance," playscript by Derek Walcott, 1996 (Box 45)
    - Hamlet, 1992-1994; 17 (Box 45)
    - Henry IV, 1994; 4 (Box 45)
    - Henry IV, 1994; 19 (Box 46)
    - Henry V, 1996; 11 (Box 46)
    - Henry V, 1995-1996; 9 (Box 47)
    - Henry VI, 1996; 23 (Box 47)
    - Julius Caesar, 1993-1996; 21 (Box 47)
    - King Lear, 1991; 2 (Box 47)
    - Lonely Planet, 1996 (Box 48)
    - Love Life, 1990; 3 (Box 48)
    - Love's Labor's Lost, 1987; 4 (Box 48)
    - Macbeth, 1969-1995; 28 (Box 48)
    - Mandragola, 1986 (Box 48)
    - Mary Stuart, 1990 (Box 48)
    - Measure for Measure, 1996; 5 (Box 48)
    - Measure for Measure, 1991-1996; 35 (Box 49)
    - The Merchant of Venice, 1988 (Box 49)
    - The Merry Wives of Windsor, 1990-1998; 3 (Box 49)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1992 (Box 49)
    - Mother Courage, 1993; 17 (Box 49)
    - Mourning Becomes Electra, 1996-1997; 7 (Box 50)
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 1992-1993; 34 (Box 50)
    - Oregon Shakespeare Festival, 1995 (Box 50)
    - Orlando Shakespeare Festival, 1988 (Box 50)
    - Otabenga, 1994; 3 (Box 50)
    - Othello, 1990-1991; 6 (Box 51)
    - Peer Gynt, 1998; 12 (Box 51)
    - A Piece of My Heart, 1990-1992 (Box 51)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1986, 1994; 16 (Box 51)
    - Richard II, 1988, 1993-1994; 7 (Box 51)
    - Richard II, 1993-1994; 11 (Box 52)
    - Richard III, 1990-1991; 4 (Box 52)
    - Saint Joan, 1991-1992; 9 (Box 52)
    - Saint Joan, 1991-1992; 8 (Box 53)
    - School For Scandal, 1994-1995; 2 (Box 53)
    - "She Talks to Beethoven," playscript by Adrienne Kennedy, undated (Box 53)
    - Showboat, 1989-1990; 2 (Box 53)
    - Sleep Deprivation Chamber, 1995-1996; 3 (Box 53)
    - Sweet Bird of Youth, undated (Box 53)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 1994-1995; 4 (Box 53)
    - The Tempest, 1987-1998; 4 (Box 53)
    - Ten by Tennessee, 1986 (Box 53)
    - 'Tis Pity She's a Whore, 1988; 2 (Box 53)
    - Titus Andronicus, 1996; 2 (Box 53)
    - "To Form a More Perfect Union, the making of the constitution," television treatment, 1989 (Box 53)
    - A Touch of the Poet, 1973 (Box 53)
    - Troilus and Cressida, 1992; 18 (Box 54)
    - The Trojan Women, undated (Box 54)
    - Twelfth Night, 1988, 1995; 18 (Box 54)
    - Vanessa, 1994-1995; 5 (Box 54)
    - Volpone, 1996; 14 (Box 54)
    - Volpone, 1996; 16 (Box 55)
    - The Winter's Tale, 1987 (Box 55)
    - Winter's Tales 1944, 1994 (Box 55)
    - The Witch of Edmonton, 1986-1987 (Box 55)
  - Shakespeare Theatre Files, 1987-1996
    - League of Resident Theatres, Nontraditional Casting Project, 1987 (Box 55)
    - Queen Elizabeth II, Royal visit, 1991 (Box 55)
    - The Maryland National Capital Park and Planning Commission, 1995 (Box 55)
    - The Shakespeare Theatre, administrative papers, 1995 March 3 (Box 55)
    - Expense Reduction, memos and minutes, 1995 (Box 55)
    - "Free For All" partnership, 1995 (Box 55)
    - Carter Barron, report, 1995 (Box 55)
    - Washington Post magazine, 1989 (Box 55)
    - The Second Shepherd's Pageant, undated (Box 55)
    - Fund raising, 1995 (Box 55)
    - "Nobody's Perfect Or Why Did the English Stage Take Boys for Women?" by Stephen Orgel, typescript, undated (Box 55)
    - Research material related to Richard II to Henry V, photocopies, undated (Box 55)
  - Speaking Engagements and Lectures, 1990-1996
    - Academy for Educational Development, 1993 (Box 56)
    - Federal City Council, 1995 (Box 56)
    - George Washington University, "Theatre Talk", 1992 (Box 56)
    - Mary Washington College Visitor in Residence, 1994 (Box 56)
    - New York University (Box 56)
    - Opera America, Miami, 1993 (Box 56)
    - The Rotary Club, 1993 (Box 56)
    - University of South Carolina, 1994, 1996; 3 (Box 56)
    - Southern Methodist University, 1992 (Box 56)
    - Thelonious Monk Institute of Jazz, 1993 (Box 56)
    - Yale University, 1990-1994 (Box 56)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1999
    - Correspondence, 1984-1996; 21 (Box 57)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1996; 53 (Box 58)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1989; 14 (Box 59)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1999; 10 (Box 60)
    - Correspondence - personal, 1996-1998; 9 (Box 60)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1995; 12 (Box 61)
    - Correspondence - engagements, 1987-1994; 8 (Box 61)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1996; 20 (Box 62)
      Includes correspondence with The Acting Company.
    - Correspondence, 1990-1998; 21 (Box 63)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992; 4 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence - Joan Kahn, 1974-1988; 7 (Box 64)
  - Subject Files, 1950-1998
    - Address books, undated; 2 (Box 64)
    - AIDS Workshop, 1988-1989 (Box 64)
    - Alabama Shakespeare Festival, 1986 (Box 64)
    - American High School Theatre Festival, 1997 (Box 64)
    - American Shakespeare Theatre, 1987 (Box 64)
    - American Voices, undated (Box 64)
    - AMS Survey, 1994 (Box 64)
    - Association for Theatre in Higher Education, 1993 (Box 64)
    - Auditions, 1986-1994; 8 (Box 64)
    - Awards: DC Mayor's Arts Awards, 1991 (Box 64)
    - Awards: John Houseman Award, 1989 (Box 64)
    - Bay City Multicultural Arts Initiative, 1990 (Box 65)
    - Bylaws of the Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, 1989 (Box 65)
    - Boards of Directors and Trustees, 1985-1991; 9 (Box 65)
    - Braithwaite, Tony, 1993 (Box 65)
    - Burglary-Insurance, 1995 (Box 65)
    - Calendars, 1987-1998; 9 (Box 65)
    - Catholic University, 1990 (Box 65)
    - Chautauqua Institution, 1985-1987 (Box 65)
    - Chernikoff & Company/Lobbyist, 1996 (Box 65)
    - Circle in the Square, 1985-1988 (Box 65)
    - Composers, 1992 (Box 65)
    - Congratulations, 1992-1993 (Box 65)
    - Consultant proposals, 1985-1990 (Box 66)
    - Contributors, 1995 (Box 66)
    - Cultural Task Force, 1990 (Box 66)
    - DC Commission on the Arts and Humanities, 1987, undated; 3 (Box 66)
    - DC Signature Theatre, 1995 (Box 66)
    - Dallas Opera/ Elektra, 1995 (Box 66)
    - Development, 1995 (Box 66)
    - Directors, 1993 (Box 66)
    - The Drama League, 1993 (Box 66)
    - Dramaturgical Fellowship, 1990 (Box 66)
    - The Duchess of Malfi, 1983-1989 (Box 66)
    - Emerson College, 1994 (Box 66)
    - England, 1996 (Box 66)
    - European vacation, 1997 (Box 66)
    - Evergreen Education Foundation, 1992 (Box 66)
    - Executive Committee meeting, Shakespeare Theatre, 1995-1998; 3 (Box 66)
    - Facilities, 1994-1995; 2 (Box 66)
    - Finance Committee, Shakespeare Theatre, 1992-1994; 3 (Box 66)
    - Financial statements, 1996-1997 (Box 66)
    - Fog research, 1994 (Box 66)
    - "Folger crisis clippings", 1985; 1 (Box 66)
    - Folger season, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 66)
    - Fuente Ovejuna, 1990-1991 (Box 66)
    - Georgians, 1991 (Box 66)
    - Gielgud Fellowship, 1997; 2 (Box 66)
    - Gilmore, Allen, 1996 (Box 66)
    - Globe Theatre reconstruction project, 1997 (Box 66)
    - Guthrie Theatre, 1988-1996; 2 (Box 66)
    - Hamburg, 1992 (Box 66)
    - Hedda Gabler, 1987 (Box 66)
    - Helen Hayes Awards, 1988-1992; 3 (Box 67)
    - Houston Grand Opera, 1985-1989 (Box 67)
    - Ibsen, undated (Box 67)
    - International visitors, 1991 (Box 67)
    - The Japan Foundation, 1989 (Box 67)
    - Jonson, Ben, undated (Box 67)
    - Juilliard School, 1985-1998; 14 (Box 67)
    - Kahn, Michael: resume, 1993 (Box 67)
    - Kennedy Center, 1990 (Box 67)
    - Krakow, Poland, Drama Teacher workshop, 1986 (Box 67)
    - The League of Resident Theatres Assoc., 1991-1997; 3 (Box 67)
    - London, 1993 (Box 67)
    - McCarter Theatre, 1993 (Box 67)
    - McGillis, Kelly, 1997 (Box 67)
    - Mercartes, 1993 (Box 67)
    - Michael Miller Project, 1993 (Box 67)
    - Miskolc Theatre Project, 1997 (Box 67)
    - MOJO, 1997 (Box 67)
    - Mount Vernon College, 1995 (Box 67)
    - Music: Carmen, undated; 2 (Box 67)
    - Music: Carmen, 1976; undated; 2 (Box 68)
    - National Conference on American Shakespeare, 1988; undated (Box 68)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1986-1996; 16 (Box 68)
    - New York University, 1986 (Box 68)
    - Nominating committee, Shakespeare Theatre, 1995 (Box 68)
    - Non-traditional casting, 1989 (Box 68)
    - Notebooks, undated; 2 (Box 69)
    - Oklahoma Arts Institution, 1993 (Box 69)
    - Otabenga, 1994-1998; 2 (Box 69)
    - Passport, 1986 (Box 69)
    - Poland Project, 1995 (Box 69)
    - Prague: Trust for Mutual Understanding, 1993 (Box 69)
    - "Problems and Possibilities: A Report on Washington's Largest Art Institutions", 1985 (Box 69)
    - Project Historic America, 1994 (Box 69)
    - Purchase orders, blank forms and memo, 1991, undated (Box 69)
    - Pushkin Drama Theatre, 1995 (Box 69)
    - Recommendation letters, 1993-1998 (Box 69)
    - Revenue and Expense Task Force, Shakespeare Theatre, 1995 (Box 69)
    - Rhode Island, travel, 1997 (Box 69)
    - Richard III Gala '93, 1992 (Box 69)
    - Royal Shakespeare Company, press, marketing and publications, 1994 (Box 69)
    - Russian Theatre Conference, 1992 (Box 69)
    - Saint Barth's, 1995, 1998; 3 (Box 69)
    - Schedules, 1990; 1995; 2 (Box 69)
    - Seattle, 1991 (Box 69)
    - Shakespeare, 1956-1998; 11 (Box 69)
      Includes material related to The Shakespeare Park Players, Shakespeare master classes, Shakespeare Awareness Week, Shakespeare Theatre Spoleto Festival, Shakespeare Quarterly and the Shakespeare Theatre Association.
    - Shubert Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 69)
    - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers Foundation, 1987-1996 (Box 69)
    - Soviet engagements, 1991 (Box 69)
    - Speaking engagements, 1993 (Box 69)
    - Staff Lists, 1994 (Box 69)
    - Steering Committee, 1985 (Box 69)
    - Summerfare, 1989 (Box 69)
    - Swine Palace, 1992 (Box 69)
    - Telephone numbers/address book, undated (Box 69)
    - Thank you's, 1992 (Box 69)
    - Theatre Census - staff questionnaire, 1993 (Box 69)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1985-1994; 6 (Box 70)
    - A Touch of the Poet, Arena Stage, 1997; 2 (Box 70)
    - Vanessa, Dallas Opera, 1993-1995; 3 (Box 70)
    - War of the Roses, 1989 (Box 70)
    - Will Awards, 1988-1998; 9 (Box 70)
    - World Arts Forum, 1991-1992; 2 (Box 70)
    - Writings on Shakespeare, 1950-1986; undated; 12 (Box 70)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre, 1994 (Box 70)
    - Young Director's Projects, 1992-1998 (Box 70)
  - Audiovisual Material, 1985-1987
    Audio and video cassette recordings: Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Audiocassettes